Retto, do you know?
你知道吗  小烈
The way adults shake hands
大人握手的方式
I don't know
不知道
Then lend me your hand
那你把手借我一下
No
不是这样
It looks like this
是像这样子喔
It's the way adult couples shake hands.
这是大人情侣的握手方式喔
Hoshino?
星乃?
I... I know
我…我知道了
Don't hold it
妳不要握了啦
There is nothing to be ashamed of, Retto
有什么好难为情的嘛  小烈
It's just a practice
这只是练习而已呀
What are you talking about…practice
妳说什么的…练习
Don't tell you
不告诉你
What the hell
什么跟什么啊
That day
那一天
For the first time in my life
我有生以来第一次
Hope to be a HERO
希望能成为一个HERO
Now, five years later
然后五年过去了
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
The first chapter "in a bright world"
第一话「在这光明普照的世界」
How do you think about, Retto
烈人你觉得呢
What do you want to ask, Date
你要问什么  伊达
I mean, the turmoil
我说那场骚动啊
Turmoil?
骚动?
It is the rumor that there's an alien, a weirdo.
就是那个不晓得是外星人  还是怪人
Or something strange, who knows
还是变态的东西四处出没的传闻啊
If it is true, it would be interesting, right
如果是真的应该挺有趣的吧
Torigoe, which girl do you like
鸟越  你喜欢哪个女孩
I'd like to pick this girl
我应该会挑这女生吧
Ask me questions and even ignore me
问我问题还无视我啊
How about you, Retto
烈人你呢
I... Forget it
我…就算了吧
What
干嘛啦
You're really tactless, every time
你真的每次都很不上道耶
I mean you did such a thing at school …
是说你们在学校做这种事…
Eww
真讨厌
Why are boys always being like that
男生为什么每次都这样啊
That's really terrible
实在有够差劲的
Enough is enough
你们也该给我适可而止了
Don’t you know other girls can’t stand you?
不晓得其他女生都很受不了你们吗
If you want to talk dirty
如果想聊下流的话题
Go to the toilet
到厕所去聊比较适合你们
Hoshino …
星乃…
You really are "Iron maiden" Hoshino Mica
真不愧是「铁处女」星乃云母
an ultra-cleanliness who won't touch anything that boy has touched
别说是男生…连男生摸过的东西都不会
let alone a boy
直接用手去碰的超洁癖主义者
Even though, because she is very beautiful
即使如此  因为她长得很漂亮
The boys who threw themselves at her were everywhere.
拜倒在她脚下的男生总是尸横遍野
Your childhood friend is this kind of person. I think you have no hope, Retto.
儿时玩伴那副德性 我看烈人你也是没指望了吧
Yes …
是啊…
Anyway, Kirara has really changed
话说回来  云母真的变了呢
She used to play with boys more often .
她以前明明比较常和男生玩在一起的
She must have suffered from those flirting boys.
她一定是受够那些色眯眯的男生了吧
True
没错
One day, Hoshino suddenly totally changed
星乃有天突然变了一个人
She used to have a very active personality
以前的她个性积极主动
We often went to other places together.
我们放学常一起绕去其他地方
Although she often played tricks on me.
两人独处时  虽然她时常会捉弄我
I like that Hoshino
但是我很喜欢这样的星乃
Hoshino
星乃同学
Are you on duty today
妳今天是值日生吧
Can you help me carry some books to the office
可以帮我将这些笔记本搬去职员办公室吗
I see
我知道了
See you so reluctant, need help?
看妳这么不情愿  要我帮忙吗
Anyway, I see you …
反正我看妳…
don't want to touch things touched by boys.
一定是不想碰男生摸过的东西吧
Enjo
炎城
If you want to carry, just carry
你想搬就搬啊
Let me speak frankly
话先说在前头
You are not allowed to reach half a meter of mine.
绝对不准你进到我的半径一公尺内
Yes, yes, yes
是是是
She is the same
她还是老样子
I mean
我说啊
You don't have to pay too much attention to other people's eyes.
妳不必太在意旁人的眼光
Even if you change more
就算妳改变再多
Hoshino is Hoshino
星乃也一样是星乃
Just like before
就和以前一样
What do you mean
这是什么意思
As if I were urging myself to change.
讲得好像是我勉强自己改变似的
No, I don't mean that
不  我这话不是这个意思
What else does that mean
那不然是什么意思
Let me clarify
我先声明
I am not different from before in my view.
我不认为自己和以前有什么不一样
You know nothing about me
你对我明明就一无所知
Don't act like you know me very well just because we are childhood friends.
不要因为我们是儿时玩伴 就摆出一副很了解我的样子
If you're doing me a favor just to talk about this nonsense
如果你帮我忙 就是为了讲这种无聊事
Then I don't need you
那你用不着帮我也无所谓
Danger
危险
Sorry, Hoshino
抱歉  星乃
It was only when I was in a hurry that I …
我情急之下才…
I really didn't mean it
我刚才真的不是故意的
Hoshi... Hoshino
星…星乃
What the hell?
搞什么啊  真是的
The reason why Hoshino changed
星乃变了一个人的原因
It's my secret with her
是我和她之间的秘密
The reason is that …
那个原因就是…
Although the show is only halfway through.
虽然节目才进行到一半
Here's your news flash
在此为您插播临时新闻
A strange man suddenly came out of Saitama City.
琦玉市有怪人突然出现了
The strange people "Kisei Chuu" that began to show five years ago
自五年前起开始出没的怪人「规制虫」
made the streets into a mess.
使街道陷入一片混乱
Doctor, please explain
博士  麻烦您进行解说
Let me said straightforwardly
我就单刀直入地说了
The Kisei Chuu is not strange people.
所谓的规制虫并不是怪人
They were aliens who invaded the earth years ago.
它们是数年前为侵略地球而来的外星人
They removed things that make people feel pornographic.
它们会将让人类感觉到色情的事物加以排除
To absorb people's Pornographic Energy
为了将人类的色情能源
That is, "H Energy"
通称「H能源」吸收殆尽
They will not hesitate to use all means.
它们会不惜使出一切手段
Go down further
再这样下去
Childlessness is getting heavier and heavier.
少子化问题将日益严重
People go to death in fear.
人类恐怕会渐渐地走向灭亡
Please calm down, Doctor
请您冷静一点  博士
In a word
总而言之
If human H energy is sucked away,
人类的H能源如果被吸走
It is very dangerous to lose the vitality of life.
将会失去生活的活力  非常的危险
Everybody, stay away from the Kisei Chuu
请各位观众千万不要接近规制虫
Thank you all for coming today
谢谢大家今天过来捧场
I will try my best to perform
我一定会努力表演的
Dropping the cram school is the right choice. -We will cheer you up.
把补习班翘掉果然是对的 -我们会为妳加油的
Thank you for cheering me on
多亏大家为我加油打气
It seems that a puppet lady has arrived.
好像有位布偶小姐来到现场了
Please kindly advise
请多指教
Kisei Chuu "Hakkou Chuu"
规制虫「发光虫」
Large Numbers of males flock together for a small number of females.
大量的雄体为了少量的雌体群聚在一起
Man is really a creature with no reason
人类真是毫无合理性可言的生物
The first song was …
那么第一首歌是…
Did you see it
刚才有看到吧
But it seems to be light?
可是好像发光了?
Did you take a picture
你有拍下来吧
Sure
当然啰
This year, I will take an examination, and I wonder what the hell I am doing.
今年就要考试了  我到底在做什么…
I have to go to the company soon...
得赶快去公司了…
What's wrong with everyone
大家是怎么了
Meimaolin's Secret New …
美喵琳的秘密新…
I'd better find a job,
还是乖乖认命找工作吧
Once pornography is taken away from humans, it’s only that level.
一旦将色情夺走人类也不过就这点程度而已
Looks like there's one left
看来好像还剩下一个人呢
Just like that one
就和那个时候一模一样
How many people have you took away his feelings so far
妳们至今从多少人类身上夺去了他们的感情
I will never …
我再也不会…
Let you do what you want
让妳们继续为所欲为了
It's just a human, don't talk big
不过只是个人类 还真是会说大话呢
Why don't I just suck up your H energy
不如就让我吸干你的H能源吧
The fragrant H energy in puberty
我向来对思春期浓郁芳香的H能源
is my favourite
情有独钟呢
Really
是吗
But before that
但是在那之前
Let's try my trick first
先尝尝我这招吧
The reason why Hoshino being like that
星乃之所以会变成那样
It's all …
这全是…
Caused by Kisei Chuu
这些规制虫造成的
How is it possible
怎么可能
I can't believe that I'm going to lose to a human
我竟然会输给区区一个人类
Is this guy...
这家伙到底是…
I'm committed to killing the Kisei Chuu…
而我是致力于歼灭规制虫的…
High school student and HERO
高中生兼HERO
"Hakkou Chuu"
「发光虫」
Saitama Branch of Guardians of the Earth
地球防卫队琦玉支部
HERO Department of Saitama Branch of Guardians of the Earth
地球防卫队琦玉支部  HERO部门
Please do something about it
拜托你快想想办法啦
This is the kind of design that would explode if you beat Kisei Chuu
这种打倒规制虫 衣服就会爆开的设计
Every time I have to take my clothes to change, Oh, crap.
每次都得带着替换衣物 真的伤脑筋耶
There is no other way, bro Retto.
这也没办法啊  烈人小弟
It turns out that "XERO GEAR" can only strengthen your body.
毕竟「XERO  GEAR」强化的也就只有你的肉体而已
Even if it is
就算是这样
The least you can do is think about me who has to run naked in the street every time
你好歹也为每次都得在街上裸奔的我想想嘛
Anyway
不过
Is such a thing worth being so embarrassed about
这种事有必要这么难为情吗
I think your clothes are embarrassing enough
我倒觉得你那身衣服就够让人难为情了
Really
是吗
All right
好了
After that, bro Retto
维护完毕了  烈人小弟
Thank you
谢谢你
By the way
对了
What's going on about adding new members
之前说要增加新成员 后来怎么样了
I am looking for it
我们现在也正在寻找候补
It's just that I can't find anyone like you.
只是一直找不到像你们这么有素质的人
Uncle, why don't you just do it yourself.
我看叔叔你干脆自己来当不就好了吗
Don't impose on others
别强人所难
The XERO GEAR
这个XERO  GEAR
can turn user's Pornographic energy
能将使用者的色情能源
"H Energy" into its own power
「H能源」转换为力量使用
Only you adolescent girls and boys use it
让烈人小弟你们这些青春期的少年少女使用
can achieve the greatest effect
才能发挥出最大的效果
Not like me, the old uncle
和我这种大叔可不一样
what's more …
再说…
You can't change the girl's Kisei Chuu
你也无法原谅改变那女孩的规制虫吧
Yes
没有错
That's why I agreed to help
我之所以会答应帮忙 就是因为这一点
I also know that even if I do these things
我也知道就算做这些
The Hoshino in the past is no longer able to return.
那个时候的星乃也已经回不来了
But
但是
I've made up my mind
我已经决定了
I won't let anyone experience this feeling again
我不会再让任何人经历这种感觉了
Even if that guy denied everything
就算那家伙否定了这一切
For me, it was also a memory of my first love that could never be replaced
对我来说 那也是无可取代的初恋回忆
Tomorrow I will apologize to her formally.
明天还是去向她郑重道歉吧
Hoshino
星乃
I'm really sorry about yesterday
昨天真的很抱歉
It's all my fault
昨天的事是我不对
Stinky boy, why are you staring at me
臭男生  干嘛一直盯着我看
nothing …
没什么…
Well …
那个…
Good morning
早安
Morning, Kirara
早啊  云母
Have you finished your language homework
妳现代国文的作业写好了吗
Of course
当然啰
But you can't copy it
不过妳别想照抄
My existence has disappeared from Hoshino's mind
我的存在从星乃的意识中消失掉了
Hoshi... Hoshino?
星…星乃?
Hoshino
星乃
Hoshino …
星乃…
People in the past said
以前的人曾经说过
The opposite of "like" is not "dislike"
「喜欢」的反义词不是「讨厌」
But "being indifferent"
而是「漠不关心」
Well... Well, I know
那…那我知道了
You don't have to answer me
妳不用回答我也没关系
It doesn't matter if you don't want to forgive me
不愿意原谅我也无所谓
But please listen to me
但是拜托妳听我说
Has Hoshino changed
星乃到底有没有变
It doesn't matter at all
这种事一点也不重要
Even if you don't want to look back
就算妳不愿意回想起
The past is also the same.
以前的往事也一样
I actually
我其实
… to Hoshino at that time
对当时的星乃…
Found you, human
找到你了  人类
You were yesterday …
妳是昨天的…
Don't worry, Hoshino
别担心  星乃
You can back off first
妳先退后吧
Come forth, Kisei Chuu
放马过来  规制虫
I won't let you hit Hoshino again
我不会再让妳们对星乃出手了
Enjo
炎城
After the exhaustion of yesterday's battle
经过昨天战斗的消耗
H-Energy is not enough, right?
H能源已经不够用了吗
You don't seem to be able to exert the power like yesterday
你好像无法发挥昨天的力量呢
In that case
既然如此
I shall now use the new body that her Majesty has given me
我现在就用女王陛下赐给我的这副新躯体
to go to the streets and absorb all H-energy.
到街上去将人类的H能源吸收殆尽
Just grind your teeth and watch
你就在一旁咬牙看着吧
The first step
那么第一步
I will absorb the female H-energy behind you.
我就先从你身后的雌体的H能源开始吸收起吧
What is it
这是什么
Run, Hoshino
快逃吧  星乃
What is the feeling
这种感觉是怎么回事
Now it's an emergency
现在明明是这种状况
But I feel …
但是我却觉得…
Enjo, your hand …
炎城  你的手…
Sorry, I'm...
抱歉  我又…
No
不是
Only this one time
仅此一次下不为例
Take my hand anyway
先继续握住我的手吧
This feeling
这种感觉
I haven't felt this way for many years
已经多少年没有过了呢
The Hand of Enjo
炎城的手
It's bigger than I thought
比我想像中还要大
It's very heavy to hold it.
握起来好沉着稳重
Body temperature passes through his hand
体温透过手传了过来
Boy's Hand
男孩子的手
Is that how it feels
原来是这种感觉吗
Because they have been connected before.
因为之前都完全没有接触
Now I become very sensitive to boys
现在反而对男孩子变得特别敏感了
But
但是
Like hands connected directly
像这样直接接触彼此的手
In some ways, it's not just a matter of holding the naked body together.
就某方面来说 不就和光着身子抱在一起一样吗
I can't stand it anymore
我实在无法再忍受了
The sealed atrium will be opened.
封闭的心房要被敞开了
What's going on
这是怎么回事
I've never seen anything like it
我也从来没看过这种状况
Is it the H-energy source of Hoshino?
难道说这是星乃的H能源
I found you
找到你们了
Wake up, human
给我觉悟吧  人类
It's getting bigger
竟然变得这么大了
She put all the people in the street...
难道她把街上的人都…
How to deal with this guy
要怎么对付这家伙
I'll tell you the reason later.
理由我待会再跟妳说明
Anyway, let's work together now
总之我们现在先同心协力
Break her down
把她打垮吧
You're awesome, Hoshino
妳好厉害啊  星乃
Hit the large-scale Kisei Chuu by a blow...
竟然一击就把那种大型规制虫…
No!
不要啊!
What the hell is it
现在到底是什么状况啦
Sorry... I got you involved in this
抱歉…把妳给牵扯进来了
But
不过
It's really a great deal to have you here.
有妳在真是帮了大忙
Really
是吗
Has he been fighting somewhere I don't know
他一直都在我不晓得的地方战斗着吗
with the monsters that attacked us…
和当时袭击我们的那些怪物…
you OK?
妳没事吧
What did that guy do to you just now
那家伙刚才好像对妳做了什么
I'm OK
我没事
Just a little bit of a shock
只是有点吓了一跳
Impossible
这怎么可能
I sucked up so much H-energy and I was able to act like nothing had happened
我吸取了这么多H能源 居然还能像这样若无其事
How could there be such a pornographic human
怎么会有这么色情的人类
This quantity is several times…tens of times as many as the average person
这个量是常人的好几倍…好几十倍
No, even more
不  甚至还要更多
What does she usually think
她平常到底都在想些什么
so that she could have such an extraordinary degree of pornography
才能有这么超乎常人的色情度
I actually have no way to suck her H-energy dry.
我竟然没有办法将她的H能源吸干
this people…
这个人类…
is out of control
无法规制
Hoshino
星乃
There is no such thing
才没有这种事
It's my heart closed
于是我为自己的心房上了锁
Began to refuse contact with men
开始拒绝与男人接触
But if …
但是  如果说…
I can go back to the old time…
还能回到以前那个时候的话…
In that case…
既…既然这样…
Let me be do a favor for Retto
我也一起来帮小烈的忙吧
But only if you promise me
不过前提是你要答应我
Don't tell anyone about what happened today
不会把今天发生的事告诉别人
Don't talk about this yet, Hoshino
先不说这个  星乃
You call me Retto …
妳刚才叫我小烈…
Nope
没这回事
I'm sorry. You forgot about it
抱歉  你忘了它吧
But you just …
可是妳刚才明明…
Enjo …
炎城…
You heard me wrong, didn't you
是你听错了对吧
Yes …
是…
Why make out
为什么在这种公共场所
with someone naked in a public place like this
光着身子跟别人在那里亲热啊
You …
妳们…
Honestly
真是的
we heard that a large Kisei Chuu appeared
亏我们听说有大型规制虫出现
so we come here to help
特地连忙赶过来
Is this girl YELLOW
这女孩就是YELLOW吗
It is YELLOW
与其说是YELLOW
It's more like "Super YELLOW"
这身体不如说是「超级YELLOW」吧
It's a rude thing to say about people you meet for the first time, Momoka
这样说初次见面的人太失礼了  百花
What's the matter with these people
这些人是怎么回事
Take it
拿去吧
Put it on while nobody come here.
趁现在还没有人过来  快点穿上吧
Thank you
谢谢妳
Well, this is the key
然后呢  这把是钥匙
What
什么
You ask me "what"
妳还问我「什么」
Didn't you hear that everyone has to live together after joining HXERO
妳没听说加入HXERO后 大家都要住在一起吗
That is to say the four of you …
那也就是说妳们四个人…
We live together
我们都住在一起
What's wrong with that
这又有什么问题吗
Enjo is a big fool.
炎城是大笨蛋
There has been people said
曾经有人这么说过
"HERO"
「HERO」这个词
It is made up of "H" and "ERO"
是由「H」和「ERO」(色情)组成的
In Saitama
在这个琦玉
There are people who are responsible for keeping the peace
有负责守护和平
HXE RED Enjo Retto
HXE  RED  炎城烈人
is H and ERO
又H又ERO的
HXE RED Hoshino Kirara
HXE  RED  星乃云母
Five Heroes
五位英雄
HXE PINK Taoyuan Momoka
HXE  PINK  桃园百花
HXE WHITE Shirayuki Maihime
HXE  WHITE  白雪舞姬
Their name is …
他们的名字就是…
HXE BLUE Sky Temple
HXE  BLUE  天空寺宙
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
The next chapter "HXEROS Gather"
下一回「HXEROS集结」